question_data = [
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Super Mario Bros. was released in 1990.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
     },
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Tony Hawk&#039;s Pro Skater was released in 1999.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In &quot;Team Fortress 2&quot;, the &quot;Bill&#039;s Hat&quot; is a reference to the game &quot;Dota 2&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Mortal Kombat was almost based on Jean-Claude Van Damme movie.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "David Baszucki was a co-founder of ROBLOX Corporation.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The ADAM collecters in the Bioshock series are known as Little Sisters.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In &quot;League of Legends&quot;, there exists four different types of Dragon.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Hidden in the files for &quot;Mario Kart Arcade GP&quot; is a picture of the Beslan school hostage crisis.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In career mode of &quot;Need for Speed: Underground 2&quot;, the first car the player can drive is the BMW M3 GTR.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In the game &quot;Until Dawn&quot; Emily is the only playable character who can be killed by another playable character directly.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
